And that was good. But then kind of
one of the questions was somebody
asked a question about language.
You know, it's kind of quite a
complicated question about, like,
how do you heighten the language when
you're writing prose and how do
you show from the language various
things? And the lady who was the
published novelist, she said, well,
what I think you should be doing is,
I think you should be telling me a
story.
and I thought this was a really
interesting idea. I mean, it's kind of
in some ways it's obvious, but I
think in other ways it's not obvious
because what I realise is that when
you're telling somebody a story,
you don't fret very much about the
language. Because you're focusing on
telling a story and everybody
essentially knows how to tell a story.
They tell stories to their
friends, tell stories to their work
colleagues, tell stories down the
pub. When we were teenagers and we
were in trouble with our parents,
we told them some kind of story.
If the police find a body under
your patio, then kind of you have to
figure out a story. You have
to keep a story straight.
And so when you're manufacturing
those stories, you're not worrying
about the language.